I think it's important
to live and die
like a human
I think it's important
to live and die
like a human
I think it's important
to live and die
like a human
I think it's important
to live and die
like a human
I think it's important
to live and die
like a human
I think it's important
to live and die
like a human
I think it's important
to live and die
like a human
I think it's important
to live and die
like a human
I think it's important
to live and die
like a human
Tou
ri
No
mura
I may not look like it,
but I am a good cook
ri
Lumière
Hika
As a beautiful genius,
there's not much I can't do
Tokiwa
ji
hou
Saih
Saihouji
Surely that in itself
will be a punishment, and a sin
i
Yukari
Momo
Because that's the only way
I can make amends
Sousuke
Hiragino
no
"All of us are going
to get out of here... alive!"
The final frontier left for mankind...
The Deep Sea
A place of beginning.
The starting point of a branch, governed by gravity.
where the fluctuations created will soon divide the boundaries.
Cold-hearted "selection" begins.
Or perhaps "culling".
Trying and failing looms as a
Logic
possibility.
extinguishes countless hopes.
And at the end of it all, there you are.
extinguishes countless  hopes.
There's no such thing as a predetermined destination.
So then how did we end up here?
By accident?
The answer is...
「In 1872, a ghost ship was discovered drifting across the Atlantic.」
「It's not a thing that happens in one generation but an inherited mutation that affects the efficiency of survival and reproduction... Sorry, that was a bit difficult, wasn't it?」
“The Fourth Day”
「...Have you ever read Camus?」
「Recently, an individual was discovered that mimicked the voice of its dead mate.」
I can't remember
There were
two survivors
I can't
One of them is
a graduate
student
named—
One of them is
a graduate
student
named—
One of them is
a graduate
student
named—
One of them is
a graduate
student
named—
One of them is
a graduate
student
named—
One of them is
a graduate
student
named—
One of them is
a graduate
student
named—
One of them is
a graduate
student
named—
One of them is
a graduate
student
named—
Who survived?
And the other one was...
If you reach the worst possible outcome
while aiming for the best, what will you do?